Alright we're going to explain a little bit about making spares.
This is a one pin spare and it's the six pin, it's on the right hand side of the lane.
The best way to make a spare is cross alley.
Six pin is on the right hand lane, so I'm going to stand on the left.
The four pin is the opposite side, it's on the left hand, I would stand on my right.
Let's show you how I make the six pin.
I'm going to stand all the way on the left hand part of the lane, I'm going to draw an imaginary line from the arrows to my pin.
I'm going to try to hit that line and make this pin.
It's easy, once you know the technique and draw that imaginary line you'll make it.
Practice where every spare on the lane, where you should stand for that spare.
So practice and practice.
The only way to learn every spare, and there's hundreds of different types of spares you need to make, so it takes a lot of practice.
But find the right place to stand for every spare for your game.
Now I'll show you, I have a one, a two, and a six.
Now anytime, I have the head pin up, I'll throw a strike ball, okay?
So if I got the head pin up, most of the times I'll throw my strike ball, because that's going to take out the head pin and anything else.
On this particular spare, I know my game and I'm going to move a little to the right, try to let my ball go to the left hand side of that head pin so I'm sure to make all three pins.
That's nice when a plan comes together.
Do it right, you'll get it done.